hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft today
is a very special episode because we are
going to be playing some golf with the
boys and the boys are isko and mumbo
jumbo if you're going golfing you've got
to dress for the occasion everyone knows
that can't go and you just your red
shirt and your grey trousers like
everyone else does you know you gotta
you gotta make it special which is why
i've got my scottish golf outfit on
[Laughter]
this is a traditional ware for scotland
golfers i love it uh i don't think many
people wear them now but it is oh
goodness me all right let's go golfing
right we're gonna go meet the boys in
town let's head on over and see if we
can find them hello
you're you're right
lads
clearly we are all ready for golf it's
gail
are you going to play tennis
you do look like a tennis player
it's either like someone dressed me up
this morning okay i woke up in these
clothes it's either and i figure it's
either tennis
yeah burn borg or you're going to boy
scouts it's like
that could also be i got a beard dude
that would be oh that's true
well in top british fashion mumbo and i
are in our scottish kilts ready for some
yup golfing
we've even got the little hats
look how cute are with our little hats
now let me question you this why am i
wearing shorts and not a kilt
because you're not british you're a
swede i think you're wearing a swedish
outfit
this is not how sweet going golf
this would be bad i mean i've had a
green card in golf i let you guys know
and
shorts are not permitted
i look like that stupid idiot who comes
on the plane it's like oh yes i got two
british friends over in britain and
we're gonna go and play some golf today
it's gonna be so fun and then i fly over
and i speak like this and i'm like hello
friends and you guys go like oh my god
seriously
wearing like look him he's not gonna get
in to any course
right i've just realized
we need to stand beneath you iskall
because you know how it is with kilts we
can't be standing too high up because
otherwise
does that mean i go first the ladder
first option
you're definitely first of the ladder
does anyone know where the golf course
is by the way oh no idea i have no clue
no
yeah no neither
yeah something like that um
[Music]
does anyone know what general direction
is turn left uh
cub made it i'm shall we check the
nether hub they might have signs there
feeling that we need to ask for
directions we've got in all the gear but
as per usual we have no idea yeah all
the gear and no idea classic yeah
i feel like we are totally lost yeah i i
think i think we got to go towards at
least cubs base i think we're just
roaming around i reckon it's probably on
this side of the map so i think that's a
good place to start if not we're gonna
have to ask x for some directions
yeah yeah yeah well i'm glad you
actually know where cub space is because
oh no i don't worry then
oh
i think it's on this side of the the i
know it's on this side right because
he's in oh oh oh oh oh concord country
club yes that's it that's my favorite
club yes every time i use one of these
boats on this thing i i think of tokyo
drift like dude
i'm all over the show my bandana
oh i almost got past you then i don't
think you can pass me
no you're you're a bit too white oh
what are you doing
all right so i guess we're here i think
the real reason that iskall's in a
different outfit to us is because he's
our caddy
is that why you brought me along
this place looks so lethal by the way
yeah this is yes do we have a bed
members of the comm corp country club
are part of an elite group of wealthy
uh oh and very good looking even more
our own
the members of
concorp country club this is getting
more and more difficult to say by the
way represent the best of the best of
the best
so this here's all the equipment we need
apparently
right i'll take the pink one at the end
driver iron wedge all right so we got
different we got different bats
oh nice it's not right that's green it's
club club sorry
i thought sorry i forgot we weren't
playing tennis
okay so yes we've got we've got ball
markers what color what color
guys there are 42 whole there are 42
pages to the rulebook you are joking
no i'm not joking guys do you want to
i'm just going to put this out there
because this book is 42 pages long
do you want to wing it
shall we wing it
i mean
i feel like we should skim read it all
right
hit ball two hole move on
but surely that's all there is to it
yeah right
yeah i mean it's golf how hard can it be
uh ff boots feather falling boots i
assume really
i don't have those
uh it's all right i'll just fly down i
guess i've got an elytra you need you
need an ender pearl in your off hand and
then a driver or a club in your other
one
um
right in your main hand hold on uh and
then hold hold right click to charge
your trident then release right click to
send the trident and propel yourself
into the air quickly after releasing
right click again to launch the
enderpearl
every time you throw a tosk using q uh
an enderpearl counts as one shot
okay the objective of this sport is to
take the least amount of shots to reach
the hole like are we the ball here i
think we're the ball this is really
fancy so we've got to go
over yonder all right lads i'm going for
it
[Laughter]
no wait wait for it
later lads
oh i'm in did you did you did you just
did you just wait twice
what
no
so you throw the riptide and then throw
the end apart yeah
all right i'm gonna stand still i'm
gonna stand still and then i'll wait for
you guys to get and get in here
you hold right click and then as soon as
you've done it you
uh you so you hold right click and i
just hit end of pearl
uh yeah hold right click and then
immediately after you've hit the
the trident then you release an end to
pearl
okay lads i think it's fair to say
we're not doing too good
so you lose two shots
dude yeah i keep accidentally hitting
ender pearls and i'm i'm actually way
worse off than where i was yeah i was
gonna say i swear i swear i could only
see his cow last time should we just
call it that we've that we've done one
more each here because we're learning
the system should we do should we do a
do-over do over let's go again all right
lads i'm gonna i'm gonna suggest
something mad here let's read the rules
yeah probably a good idea to be quite
frankly honest with you
42 pages here we come
all right all right i'm going to play
some elevator music while i read this
[Music]
all right are we good to go uh i think
i've read the rules okay do you know
what we're doing kind of maybe i i know
what we're doing we have to look back at
the book for the different block types
yeah so apparently if you land on the
the block type you land on determines
what you're allowed to do next that's
all we need to remember and then we can
we can identify it as we go green you go
first no i reckon all three of us should
go at the same time
mad lads together right come on oh and
you get
right and remember that in the in the in
the rule book it says that you should be
able to travel 220 blocks from this okay
thanks for letting us know
thanks
we did like 50 blocks in our test run i
know yeah all right green screen i'm
charging oh okay ready i'm hang going
three oh
oh no i accidentally
i didn't even go hey iskall what's going
on i accidentally fired an enderpearl
right so that's not great
i actually did really well i'm i'm near
the hole
really yeah hang on
no i did it right
i did how do you meant to do it uh oh
well did you read the rule book mumbo
i did try my best to but
mumbo oh wow
okay well that works
this was my first shot oh there's this
girl
am i doing good am i doing good yeah
that was a good shot to be fair
where's it gonna go
what the look at though this was my
first shot
how did you land on top of that thing
dude what no i made this
well wait hang on okay what do you mean
you made it i want to be able to see
what you guys are up to because i'm i
could okay fair enough okay go on then
oh dear
[Laughter]
mumbo well
that's not come out
go and then i'm waiting
[Laughter]
oh my goodness
okay mambo you could take you you take
the first first no no no no i want to
watch you i want to watch what you're
doing okay
okay so the hole is right uh i'm gonna
hit grian's pillar that would be
hilarious
all right here we go here we go
shot number three
oh that's overshooting it that's what i
was gonna say let's go wait
i think you're going to a different hole
i think
i didn't look where the hole went
i'm all the way over here i think you're
on a different course oh wait hello
you're in a tree
i think i have to go from the floor now
by the way shot number two lads okay
yeah yeah
uh all right all right all right i i got
this voice
that was silly
it didn't it didn't go nearly as far as
i thought korean i don't know where
mumbo is he's
probably it's probably missed
oh mumbo that was so slick that was nice
hey hey hey hey
brian i'm here on this okay
all right
oh you've left them you've left it
you've left a dude behind i'm being
attacked by your your endomite whatever
it is
right okay
and
oh throw it in throw it in
there we go
number five and six
that gotta count come on no because you
need to land on the iron but that's
stupid and a real golf course the hole
is now where the pole is
i hit the pole as well i hit the pole as
well whatever whatever okay seven shots
what seven shots all right this is my
fourth
[Laughter]
all right all right all right guys that
was so pathetic
i wish you had missed then as well yeah
it was five well according to golf rules
the order of which we are uh teeing off
here is mr mambo goes first all at the
same time
oh my goodness
again
oh no oh no
lads
that's going to be so bad and the pearl
entered orbit
yes does anyone know where i am
right boys here we go oh i see you guys
oh that was a good one mambo yeah no i'm
not messing around
now green if you get this in somehow
like if you get
then i will give you 32 diamonds if you
hit the pole
yeah you definitely still the furthest
away
shot number three here he comes
it was
really awful
that was pretty bad leave me alone
hey you can't go from a tree oh my word
that was actually quite a good shot if
it wasn't illegal
that was pretty decent
i'm going for it i'm i don't care
okay i'm taking all right look at me
then i'm having this shot four
four shots
and okay i'm on four let's
yeah you're on four
mumbo you're next
oh
oh god
so do you have to land on on the like
from from this angle i can't land on the
thing yeah that's your problem not us
i'm gonna try i'm gonna try a thing i'm
gonna throw a carrot for no reason oh
that's like oh
i see what you're doing there you're
trying to feel it out welcome you're
welcome no no i'm feeding you dude
[Music]
he's come up with a plan is that two
have you just got a birdie that's two i
got a birdie
you kidding me
i did the same i've never seen someone
balance on the edge of a block quite
that much before
[Music]
no that's that's that's gold for you
they're super rude they're like
challenge please yeah very good okay
here we go
it's an interesting technique that uh
iskall has employed and it has not paid
off in the slightest yeah hold on let
the end of her land there we go where
are you oh and oh that was terrible
all right i'm going i'm gonna
you know what that oh my word that's
such a good shot that might not be bad
that's such a good shot oh
nice
oh oh oh oh
oh
dear
no
that's not that's not the end of this
it's not awful
okay oh
no
you gotta be kidding me
[Music]
what
how is that lucky dude i land look at
what i landed look at the little
aladdin does that count that's gotta
count right that gotta count no that
does not count that does not count it
does not count
he's stuck on the end rod ledge
yeah look at me i haven't moved uh this
is actually quite a tricky shot for me
here
yeah
it's very far up i think
there he goes
oh
nice
so
four for me no wait three no three three
one two three nice four i've got bogey
green three you might want to pick that
you just don't need it yeah i gotta
come back two for me
right where on earth is this this is a
bit of a long one oh my goodness i'm
going for it
that doesn't count that doesn't count
all right
here he goes oh i'm out lads
it's funny to see you just fall down
slowly i'll see you in a minute guys
oh my goodness oh my word did you see
how far that ender pearl went
green terracotta
what can you see where i am look how
much further i went new where are you no
i don't even see you
look i'm up on this tree
no i i
oh i don't know
oh wow okay okay so i'm next then
because my shot was worse can we just
stop for a second and like notice like
this must have taken cub hours
yeah yes yeah it would have taken a very
long time
but he is the grinder of hermitcraft
let's let's be real
uh which direction am i going
this direction where i'm at here
i'm just going to guess i'm just
guessing completely that was a good
guess there is literally no reasonable
way in which i can make a shock let's go
let's go let's go hey dude
you're
is that shot five
oh close
ah
okay well i've done three shots but i
landed in water so i have to
um
oh mambo
can you throw it from there
oh yes
[Laughter]
that's six
six okay so i i have done two shots but
i've landed in the water so i think i'm
on three i'm only allowed to use the
wedge i think
i think i'm gonna go for a crazy tactic
oh no that wasn't a crazy tactic i
didn't mean to do that but that was that
was perfect
what happened
what does the rule say about the flags
yeah
if you land on the flag
if you land on the flag you get you get
you you get it i think one on it yeah
yeah fair that's quite difficult yeah
i think it probably would have landed in
do i get that do you give me yeah yeah
you get that yeah all right that's four
i like how we're just making up the
rules as we go along
i'm doing shot number five but with
penalty so yeah shot number six
not a good throw it's going
centimeters off of this
hold on can i
oh no
it's painful
oh
okay is that double bogey triple bogey
triple bogey yeah seriously pick your
nose
all right i'll do it all right green's
going first and in typical fashion he is
overshooting massively
you hold your tongue
this is gone
don't you charge that side does that
mean
silence that does look very similar to
the silence
come on cool guys don't look at
explosions you know
that's definitely landed in the water
yeah i'm deep
[Applause]
oh that's good i think that's good
that's not a it's not he's over shot
he's over shot oh my word i was so close
i'm two blocks away no oh
i'm not even joking
i could have got a beacon
okay here on this scale
no no the wedge is bad that's why i got
nine shots last time
yeah yeah that's good yeah nice work
he looks right up my my my kilt yeah i
did i was a little bit close for comfort
you appeared under my guilt
so i have no idea how many shots you've
taken graham but
pretty good
all right so that was wait for i went
one
two
three four
but i get a penalty first time i was in
the water so six yeah two penalties okay
all right am i furthest or you furthest
mumble i mean
we could do some pythagoras or i could
just throw my ender pelt okay
nice
okay let's see if i can do the same
oh it's a good throw it's a solid throw
two for you guys nicely done guys yeah
so are we both twofers yeah you're a
twofers two little birds
in what direction though is it i don't
see that
what the heck is just like that goodbye
oh i see the fairway i've not done badly
guys
that's okay that's going to be good
wait where's he going
oh my god that will not go away
that's not an easy shot that is a tricky
one i don't even know where the hole is
i'm guessing it's up there on that yeah
i can i think i can choose to the left
oh it's up here big mountain yeah yeah
it's up here okay here i come here come
lads
[Music]
come on come on
i wouldn't know where that landed
someone figured
right green have you collected this
stuff um how did you do that it's it's a
mess it's a real mess
really yeah and there's no i had so much
stuff in my inventory as well
why were you bringing that much stuff
with you man
i have no idea how i died
unless oh man you did have a lot of
diamonds on you didn't you yeah why on
earth yeah that might be
like 64 plus 40. i totally i i
discovered it when we were in the
shopping district i was like why why is
my inventory full of diamonds
all right go on
back from the dead ready
back from the dead beyonce
again
the great return
all right here i go here we go
oh it's a good throw
yep
okay so you guys don't have to get my
items i'm i'm good
this is ridiculous though so you don't
have full health again you died
you can't fault you do you realize how
high up you're falling from man
like you're falling from like a hundred
blocks
you can't say there's something wrong
you launch yourself into the sky and
then fall onto the floor i'm saying the
game is badly designed there should be
slime blocks or queen box there okay i
wait look mumbo how did he get back that
quickly
yeah he's a freak of nature
a real freaking nature how did you get
that back that fast mumbo if we were
waiting for you i'm just gonna put it
out there we've been waiting ten minutes
i'm going to
this is just bad game design okay so i'm
just gonna dig this out and put water
here
okay so you're gonna just you're gonna
you're gonna change the the golf course
to your next
not change it fix it because if you
throw
come on there is those wheat blocks in
the wrong place
we see that mumbo he's losing so he's
changing the course
change is the course around my needs
because i'm the one that keeps dying
because i'm useless
wow
wow the roughness
the roughness
look how high he goes green all right
how high he goes now he expects to
survive it it's ridiculous isn't it i
didn't invite his scalp because he was
good at golf
look look he expects to survive that
yeah i know
now the gold stairs is fixed it's so
ridiculous nice
everything is good it's like jumping off
the empire state spill and being like oh
i brought my umbrella
what's wrong i've got i've got some
crocs on why am i wrong
i landed croc first
what was wrong with that
i landed crooks first
all right i'm gonna go for it guys
yes all right that might be an overshoot
is it on top of that mountain i still
don't see the flag now it's quite far
back actually i am
very close
can i just can i just finish my energy
so i can come and watch
cool i got three
you've
yeah yeah that's the plan all right
what it's kind of quite
the pressure definitely feels like it's
on with you
just standing there going
[Laughter]
oh
i hit a tree wait
ah
that was close though that's unlucky
oh but you can you can break the canopy
and throw throw your pearl from there
oh yeah you can yeah i have to go from
underneath
yeah you can do this
okay and
i'll give you that i'll get i'll give
you that yeah yeah
oh there you go oh yeah the wind blew me
yeah the wind blew in the wind blew me
in
yeah all right my number third three i
think that was my third shot as well
nice nice
iscal straight up had two shots at the
start and you died i was gonna say
it wasn't bad design i'm entering it in
the book and after that it can't be
changed green three mambo three is
called three good okay next next hole
okay
this one is a par three and there is the
hole over there wait this is a crazy
landscape by the way like what yeah
savannah mega hills wait is that it over
there can i see it
yeah yeah to the left
i see it with 18 i'm just pointing in
the right north is off it's off over
there
it's all wrong yeah it's over there
right here right where i'm standing is
the flag yeah over here somewhere just
fire it in that general direction and
hope for the best it's a good shot
ow that looked good
and i need to pick yourself up dude
uh oh i've overshot a little bit
oh so you're gonna do it like this i was
just gonna free i was gonna free ball it
yeah well i have a stupid dream in front
of me and you're killed up my face
how do you like this
that
was not good that was terrible
all right well i've done two
alright okay so it's my turn then yes
now number four his second shot on the
seventh hole
and
is this the seventh hole is it yeah yeah
he's gonna go for the free putter
he's gonna say because that's quite that
adds a little bit of a challenge to it
it's a difficult shot here in the rough
and the mustache man makes his way to
make his second shot and he's gone
outcomes
and oh my god i see this wow next to the
hole now some have been calling
some have been calling him the golfer of
our generation
can i can i dunk it yeah go ahead
oh that was almost embarrassing
all right so three points to me or three
three shots for me
if i if i just ended the top of the flag
uh no didn't quite
[Music]
oh it covers
we have to go we have to go straight
through there
i can't really tell 60 yards
yeah yeah we have to go through the
mountain
this is the mountain right here or over
the mountain i'm going over later nerds
oh no wait
wait a second
i'll see you in a bit okay right
um
hello dude yeah that was just a bit
embarrassing to be honest with you i
can't believe you call us a
nerd where are you i don't know i'm on
top of the mountains
guys okay guys this is um
just a bit of friendly go through the
mountain
yeah all right we under we understood
that without yeah yeah okay i wasn't
seriously gonna go over that ridiculous
mountain
mom it's your turn i mean can you
imagine thinking that that was a good
plan
oh my god i'm so close to the whole
house oh my god really
yeah hold on yeah can you see me yeah i
can see
dude yeah you could do a handy pal yeah
all right you reckon
yeah all right because you're so far up
what try and try and hand purl it over
the top of that one because it's kind of
in the way
oh
no i shouldn't have done that i
shouldn't have done that
guys i should not have done that
oh
there's your enemy
where are you i mean
yeah
yeah that's pretty good
here right over the edge of this
mountain okay we're pretty close is your
throw again green oh dude i've only got
one ender pearl left oh no i've got 11
left
here comes green with his third shot and
he's gonna go for the
iron and it is a oh decision-based shop
pretty bad i don't know where you just
gone i'm right here i'm behind you
my turn oh yeah
that was pretty good that was very close
to the part that's decent that's right
and i can make this with a
just uh where are you shot
oh my goodness yeah
not not terrible
all right oh wow oh that's a gift that's
it i thought yeah i saw the enderpearl
land on the plate yeah me too that's it
right
that was four uh four maybe yeah four
for me is this mumbo second
yep two seconds
oh mumbo's gonna steal the win
my throat am i actually winning i feel
like i can't be winning
that's it that's what that counts
that's it
what am i standing on
yeah you were you were like standing on
the air floating okay uh last time
oh man the final hole does it dude okay
ever just so everyone knows cub told us
this would take about 25 minutes and
we've been going for about two hours
yeah two hours
this feels a lot like real golf
oh my god this is a 600 block
one look at this
okay again cub placed every single one
of these blocks by hand
that's so sick
it's crazy like in in like a positive
way is in like that's ridiculous not
like cub you nutcase what kind of cubby
yeah yeah i'm kind of saying cub you're
not a case
where even are we
okay so we got to go back here it's this
way the flag must be this way
yeah can we can we can we scope this one
out i feel like this one needs to scope
in yeah yeah yeah i'm going to go for a
little fly around sure oh i just
oh my goodness someone flew over me
there is lava on the way here by the way
that's literally zero fun because you
have all your diamonds
so if you die in the lava i will not be
able to stop laughing for a full week
but
if i could give you that to you mumbai
i'd be happy
all right are we ready good idea
yep i i've only got eleven ender pearls
on me at this point in time which
may not be enough
there are more is that a good one is
that a good one
oh no
what the yes
i'm on the green
you're not you're on the green or on the
fairway sorry the fair d i don't know
the terms i might have
two very different things i'm on the
green bit
okay all right i think i might start
this off with a wedge
really really you want the driving i
barely made it bad i'm in the water oh
this girl
where's mumbo
i'm on my way
he's taking the mick out of me but he
hasn't even teed off
so i landed right next to her characters
that could have been bad news
all right i'm taking my second shot
super far away
and
that was i think that was a decent shot
yeah i was about to say that looked
pretty good to me let's go let's go why
didn't miami let's go let's just go okay
hello where did he go
i can see the flag
can you see the flag from there yep
oh mambo not again you're in you're on
the sound no that's a penalty i'm in the
water
where do i even need to go from here
oh that you're pretty good you need to
go
yeah yeah but it's my shot my shots
first i'm furthest away
wedge for us again though
okay
that was such a funny noise give me a
sec so i was
i was over that long bit of seagrass i
just want to see where the hole is
because i can't even see the hole
and here we see the throw made
completely of course he's going to end
up on an iceberg
this is the kind of shot that we expect
from our mustache friend
where is it even gone oh my word i'm at
the bottom of the ocean
yep
it's another penalty you better keep
track of your shots dude oh dude yeah
well i'm on
four i'm on two
wait how are you on four you've got
surely got two penalties
oh yeah no i'm five then
i'm on five now as well
okay i'm doing it green i guess you're
further ahead than me right yeah yeah
secret secret golf pro and here we see
the sweden shorts making his fifth
attempt
it's a good shot
it's a good driver
[Laughter]
and he's made it across the waterway
with clear view to the end
this is the kind of shot we've come to
expect from the sweden shorts
[Laughter]
that's ridiculous
all right here he goes silence for the
green master
[Laughter]
good throw good arc good arc on the pal
oh
wow
i'm so close
yeah that deserved an easy clap
right
the mustache
oh nice
[Applause]
that was the worst thing i've ever seen
in my life
dude i didn't know i didn't even have my
enderpearl in my office i had to switch
to it in my toolbar oh that was that was
painful to watch man
oh but he's made up for it with a
cracking throw
i think i'm gonna eyeball this one
go on mumbo
some say that his facial hair allows him
to yes guess exactly
yes
i saw that handy burn go over my head
and i'm so happy because you took the
care of me
no wait wait wait wait wait i need to
retake that because i threw my
enderphile and it hit you
yeah just give me
huh what are you doing all right no this
this enderphile that i just threw it
crashed into you instead of going into
something i saw it i saw it but you
threw like no dude
dang it i didn't have my hands on the
keyboard
you know what i saw it coming sweet
vengeance you were taking the look at me
[Laughter]
i'm just gonna let that happen
i thought you had it
i just heard that
oh man well
i'm going to take my shots okay
yeah yeah yeah
far away i can just see if i jump
seriously
oh
bad throw that doesn't count you're not
quite on the edge you're on the block
okay so that was four for me believe it
or not
that's incredible that's a birdie yeah
that was four genuinely four
yeah well
you can pick up that stuff and then so
i'm on like eight or nine i think nine
yeah nine
so ten
oh well i i i yeah i think i'm on eight
or
seven i heard you were on well you've
died and you this time you died and
destroyed part of the course this time i
was wiping tears with cotton balls off
my face there is no such thing in the
room box yeah
[Laughter]
see now i feel now i feel segregated
here
wow the swedes i mean he wore shorts to
golf dude
yeah what the heck
what a jerk yeah i know look with
surrounded groom we are surrounded by
icebergs and this dude's in shorts
i mean seriously
like come on now call a viking country
for a reason
oh wait there's a chest i think there's
chest at the end is this the end yeah
yeah there's a chest at the end put your
score here include name score and rule
type were we using
oh the additional rules you can add in
is this all my stuff
we did normal rules i guess
yeah but we also had a few additional
ones that was a lot like genuine golf
where it took two hours
and we sucked
yeah
yeah i feel like that was yeah very
similar to real golf experiences that
i've had what do you mean we sucked we
had some really good shots though and by
the way let me finish okay oh yeah
okay
you haven't done it yet is it no is it
number eight or is it number
number i heard it was number eleven
definitely not are you gonna throw it
are you going through it
yeah i'm gonna throw it god
that no oh no oh that's embarrassing
oh that's
sorry about that no no no no no no hang
on a minute
we need to
[Laughter]
all right so that's 12.
that's that's
nine hold on how many did you get number
uh no not 12.
i think it was 12 right 12. no it was
like it was a 10 i think it was 10
wasn't it was it 10 is 10 no definitely
not 10. he would land in the water three
times
that's six shots just in the water it's
very true i thought yeah eleven i
thought you said the max was nine
yeah but but then both me and mambo had
a lot so now we're gonna i'm gonna count
this together elevate your music please
okay dude
how is he good in mathematicians
helping very much
why do we do a song of numbers just to
really throw him off
i feel like this is a good time to
practice our three times table green oh
yeah yeah and just three
six
uh
nine nailed it
you guys are the worst 18
21 oh i've seriously messed something up
dang it
there we go okay
right let's move on to the fours
and a four and an eight and a twelve
yeah we're the we're the worst people to
be sat next to like a maths class that's
for sure
okay okay i'm gonna add it together now
can we can we get some guesses because
we're just gonna go whoever had the
least amount of shots right we're not
gonna care about par or anything no okay
yeah yeah
i guess that i got
uh
i'm thinking iskall maybe one
yeah i think iskall probably won
okay
i don't know yet i've added up
oh you've still got one person i know
one person didn't win so let me just let
me just let me just just just just
clarify you're adding nine numbers
together and it's taking you what half
an hour
yeah because you guys keep doing
annoying stuff
like getting up all in your grill all
right here's the fire jump in front of
you with michael
monday final score
okay
up until the last
hole iskall was heavily in the lead
mambo was dead last
the finals remained dead last for nine
holes
mambo nescal came in on 42 shots was
green took the victory on 39.
oh that's quite close that is really
close that is ghost that is good we
killed it yeah
nicely done guys how do we compare to
everyone else
cub got 33
of course oh wait zombie he built 33
i think that's an example yeah i think
oh yeah that is the example my bad it
says exampled above it okay so it's only
cub that's actually played
yeah and if you you want oh yeah no no
no no
cleo is an example okay
but then again you know
also has had two tries in it yeah it's
true yeah and he's designed it
yeah
so you add at least 25 points to that
i'm adding your mambo for you because
okay there we go
remember that i played on really really
hard rules make sure you include that
there you go 93 for
goodness sake
all right well we can leave that be
good good good game good we need to
return our clubs and stuff now
yeah oh our bats our rackets that's a
lot of election points here you got it
you gotta admit like getting trends is
really tough
so yeah
mad
wedge iron trident oh wait no that's my
trident
i was unintentionally
oh wait my mind would be called wedge
iron subscribe
oh wait i should put the bed back
in my car in my country of sweden it is
uh
custom to wear shorts at the golf course
and to honor the winner
with some bling bling yeah oh here is
for the winner 20 diamonds from me
and
thank you
that was a lot of fun gg
yeah that was great fun yeah that was
hilarious
oh i need to put the ice back
oh yeah yeah i've used up all of mine
well i think i think we're done here i
think i think we can successfully leave
this place
we have a successful golfing session and
never come back
i think i'm gonna be here every night
practicing and then we're gonna go
another round and i'm not gonna be
wearing shorts next time okay okay all
right okay
yeah because they are awful never wear
them again
and with that lately
i think it is time to end
see you boys later
bye
you